#### Contact

35991008207 (Mobile) guir.vilela@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ guilhermeribeirovilela (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

React.js Next.js Web developer

# Guilherme Ribeiro Vilela

Mid-level Front-end Web and Mobile Next.js | React Native Varginha, Minas Gerais, Brazil

## Summary

Front-end Web and Mobile developer with 5 years of experience. Specialized in JavaScript, React/Next.js, Angular 11, Jest, and Cypress. Proficient in Scrum, with experience in mentoring and unit test training. Professional with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from UNIS-MG in Varginha.

# Experience

Hubert Administração de Condomínios e Imóveis Mid-level Front-end Web and Mobile Next.js | Angular | React Native November 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months) São Paulo, Brasil

✓ Develop the projects proposed in the company using the REACT/Next, Angular (11), and React Native framework. StyledComponents, HTML, CSS, NPM, GIT, and integration with Rest API.

- ✓ Meetups, responsible for instructing the team on unit testing.
- ✓ Implement front end Storybook documentation.
- ✓ Azure management, and Azure panel.
- ✓ Developing new templates for the website.
- ✓ Dynamic templates based on Rest API data.
- ✓ Agile method: Scrum in squads, with task division through Azure Boards.
- ✓ Projects developed with Hooks, Controllers, Services, Components, Clean Code Mocks, Rest API.
- ✓ Projects with multiple languages using i18n.

#### i476

Mid-level Development Analyst July 2021 - November 2022 (1 year 5 months) Nova Lima, Minas Gerais, Brasil

- ✓ Develop the projects proposed in the company using the ANGULAR (11), SASS, HTML, CSS, YARN, JIRA, GIT framework, and integration with Rest API.
- ✓ Develop dashboards with graphics.
- ✓ Develop new templates for the website.

- ✓ Dynamic templates based on Rest API data.
- ✓ System used: Ubuntu.
- ✓ Agile method: Scrum, with task division through Trello and Jira.
- ✓ Developer of the partner company's financial app using React Native.
- $\checkmark \ \mathsf{App} \ \mathsf{developed} \ \mathsf{with} \ \mathsf{StyleSheet}, \ \mathsf{ThemeProvider}, \ \mathsf{Redux}, \ \mathsf{Hooks}, \\$

Components, Clean Code, Rest API.

### Simplifica Fretes

Front-end Web Developer | Angular March 2020 - July 2021 (1 year 5 months)

Varginha, Minas Gerais, Brasil

- ✓ Develop the proposed projects in the startup using the ANGULAR (5.4), SASS, HTML, CSS, YARN, BITBUCKET, GIT framework, and integration with Rest API.
- ✓ Host server maintenance for the platform.
- ✓ Responsible for testing the application and deploying it to the production platform.
- ✓ Develop dashboards with graphs.
- ✓ Develop a subscription platform.
- ✓ Develop new templates for the website.
- ✓ Dynamic templates based on Rest API data.
- ✓ Ubuntu Operational System.
- ✓ Using Agile method: Scrum, with task division using Trello, 2-week sprints. Responsible for implementing Scrum in the company.
- ✓ Using WebSocket for real-time applications.

#### Wizzer Imóveis

Front-end Web Developer | Vue.js June 2019 - February 2020 (9 months)

Varginha

- ✓ Develop the proposed projects in the startup using the Vue.js framework, SASS, HTML, CSS, YARN, GIT.
- ✓ Developing layouts.
- ✓ Participating in the meetup organized by the team to discuss Vue.js.
- ✓ Reporting to the owner

#### Diretriz

Information Technology Technician August 2018 - February 2019 (7 months)

Varginha e Região, Brasil

- ✓ Maintenance of computers, networks, PABX, printers, and peripherals.
- ✓ Help Desk management and support.
- ✓ Reporting to the Coordinator.

ICC Solutions Ltd Computer Instructor August 2016 - June 2017 (11 months)

Varginha e Região, Brasil

✓Computer Science Teacher in Microsoft Office: Excel 2016, Word 2016, PowerPoint 2016, CorelDraw, Video Editing in Filmora.

✓ Reporting to the Coordinator.

### Education

Grupo Educacional Unis

Bacharelado, Ciência da Computação · (February 2018 - February 2022)